Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory01
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents A
  - American Comm. for Anti-Nazi Literature (Box 2)
    - Financial report, 1936 May 7; 1p
    - Minutes, 1936 May 11; 2p
    - Minutes, 1936 May 18; 1p
    - ?, 1936 May 18
    - Minutes, 1936 May 25; 2p
    - Minutes, 1936 June 1; 2p
    - Minutes, 1936 June 8; 1p
    - Minutes (enc. sponsors), 1936 July 6; 3p
    - Minutes, 1936 Aug. 3; 2p
      - (enc. with Leibner, M., 8-6-36)
    - Minutes (enc. with Leibner, M. 9-3-36), 1936 Aug. 31; 2p
    - Minutes (enc. with Leibner, M. 9-21-36), 1936 Sep. 14; 2p
    - Minutes, 1936 Oct. 13; 3p
    - Minutes, 1936 Oct. 26; 1p
    - Minutes special meeting, 1936 Nov. 16; 2p
    - Press release, 1936 Dec.??; 1p
    - Summary, 1939 Dec.??; 4p
  - American Comm. for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom (Box 2)
    - Estimated budget, 1939 Mar. 15; 3p
    - Agenda, 1939 Apr. 2; 1p
    - Report (See Boas, F.), 1939 Dec.???
    - From Mitchell, Jas. A., 1941 Jan. 17
    - From Gideonse, H.D., 1941 Oct. 23
    - Statements of Coudert and Gideonse, 1941 Sept.?
    - Dearborn, N.H., 1941 Oct. 25
    - Dearborn, N.H., 1941 Oct.???
    - Dearborn, N.H., 1941 Nov. 5
    - Program, songs of freedom, 1941 Nov. 11; 1p
    - Minutes, 1941 Nov. 11; 2p
    - Comas, Juan, 1941 Dec.???
      see also [Columbia] University Federation for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom
  - American Comm. to Save Refugees (Box 2)
    - From Boas to Gardenas, J.F. de which see, 1940 Dec. 5
  - American Comm. for World Congress Against War (Box 2)
    Signed: Dreiser, T. and Cowley, M.
    - Telegram, 1932 May 27
  - American Common, NY World's Fair, --, 1940 (Box 2)
    - Enc. with Anerson, Harvey W., 1940 May 13
  - American Community (Box 2)
    - Minutes, 1929 Nov. 15 & 25
    - Enc. in Lowenberg, E. Research probelms..., 1929 Dec. 13
    - Report, 1929 Dec. 13
    - Conference, peace movement, 1929 Dec. 15
    - Study, 1930; 4p
    - Minutes, 1930 Jan. 10
    - Report, 1930 Mar. 3; 4p
    - Minutes, 1930 Mar. 13; 2p
    - see Penningroth, P.W., 1930 June 1
    - Minutes, 1930 Oct. 14; 2p
    - Letter no. 2, 1930 Nov. 19; 2p
    - Plans, 1930 Dec.???; 1p
    - from Penningroth, P.W., 1930 Dec.???
  - American Convalescent Home for Vienna's Children (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 21; 1p
  - American Coun. of Learned Societies (Box 2)
    - Ways & Means Comm., 1920 Mar.???; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 4; 1p
    - Draft of announ. of grant from... for res. on Indian languages, 1927 June??
    - From Rosales, R.C., 1933 Aug. 11
    - Herskovits, 1937 Feb. 15; 2p
      General note
      Missing 4/8/88
    - From Leland, W.G., 1938 Feb. 3
    - From Leland, W.G., 1938 Feb. 4
    - Grants-in-Aid, 1941 May 12; 1p
    - From Huot, Martha, 1941 May 14
    - From Boas to Comm. on American Ind. lang., 1938 Mar. 28; 1p
    - see Goodchild, D, 1940 Feb. 29
    - see Goodchild, D, 1940 May 16
    - see Augustin, J.J., 1940 Dec. 2
    - Report, 1941 Jan.; 3p
    - from Prentice, Wm. K., 1941 July 12
      see also
      Brock, Wallace D.
      Graves, Mortimer
      Leland, Waldo G.
  - American E. Asiatic Assn. (Box 2)
    - Minutes, 1904 Feb. 3; 1p
  - American Economic Assn. (Box 2)
    - From Mayo-Smith, R., 1898 Mar. 22; 2p
    - From Mayo-Smith, R., 1898 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Mayo-Smith, R., 1898 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Mayo-Smith, R., 1898 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Mayo-Smith, R., 1898 Dec. 24; 1p
  - American Economic Rev. (Box 2)
    see Dewey, Davis R.
  - American Ethnological Soc. (Box 2)
    - Hist. Dept., Iowa, 1908 Oct. 9
    - see Brill, E.J., 1920 Aug. 31
    - fund solicitation, 1930 June 30; 1p
    - see Boas, F. to Pearl, R., 1931 Oct. 6
    - Resolution on death of Boas, F., 1943 Jan. 20; 1p
  - American Eugenics Soc., Inc. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 19; 1p
  - American Express Co. (Box 2)
    - 2 receipts, 1912 Mar. 2
    - 1 receipts, 1907 Jan. 4
  - American Federation of Teachers Conven. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1940 Aug. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 July 31
  - American Folk-Lore Soc. (Box 2)
    - Draft, program, 1898 Dec. 28; 1p
    - Announcement, 1898 Dec. 29; 1p
    - Announcement, 1899 Dec. 28; 1p
    - Boas to Council, 1912 Dec.; 6p
    - Treasurer's Report
      - signed: Togger, A.M.
    - Treasurer's Report, 1916 Feb. 5
    - From Boas, 1916 Nov. 17
    - Receipt from Espinosa, A.M., 1917 Mar. 17
    - From Kessler, Charles N., 1918 Apr. 14
    - see Tozzer, A.M., 1918 Dec. 12
    - see Tozzer, A.M., 1920 Nov. 23
    - postage bill, 1921 Mar. 18; 1p
    - see Lancaster Press, Inc. bill, 1926 Aug. 19
    - leftover folk-lore material, script, 1922?
    - Report signed Herzog, George, 1940 Feb.
  - American Friends Service (Box 2)
    - Telegram, 1940 Mar. 22
      See Hepburn, A. Barton
      See Thomas, Wilbur K.
  - American Geographical Society (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 20; 1p
      See Bowman, Isaiah
  - American German Student Exchange (Box 2)
    See Palmer, Archie M.
  - American Guild for Cultural Freedom (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1937 Dec. 22; 1p
  - American Historical Review (Box 2)
    See Jameson, J.E.
    See MacMillan Company
  - American Indian Linguistics (Box 2)
    - List found at end of May 1937
  - American Interracial Seminar (Box 2)
    - See Herring, H.C., 1930 Sept. 10
  - American Indian Defense Assoc. (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1932 January 22; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan; 8p
  - American Jewish Alliance (Box 2)
    - Paper to be read at meeting, 1939 Nov. 14; 2p
  - American Jewish Committee (Box 2)
    - Nazi Germany's latest anti-Jewish measures (Bul. 35-4), 1935 Dec.???; 6p
    - see Anon. to Mond, Robt., 1937 May 5
    - Papers, 1937 Mar.???; 6p
    - see Scheniderman, Harry, 1935 Mar. 27
    - Papers, 1935 Mar. 29
    - Papers, 1935 Apr. 9
    - Papers, 1935 Apr. 11
    - Papers, 1935 Apr. 26
    - Papers, 1935 July 9
      see Wallach, Sidney
  - American Jewish Joint Distribution Comm. (Box 2)
    - see Hyman, J.C., 1933 May 10
  - American Journal of Archaeology (Box 2)
    - Special rates for back numbers, 1p
      see Bowditch, Charles P.
  - American Journal of Botany (Box 2)
    see Gager, C. Stuart
  - American Journal of International Law (Box 2)
    see Scott, James Brown
  - American Journal of Science (Box 2)
    see Dana, E.S.
  - American Jour. of Semitic Languages and Literatures (Box 2)
    see Smith, J.M. Powis
  - American Jour. of Sociology (Box 2)
    - From Boas to Book Rev. Editor, 1935 May 1; 1p
  - American Labor Party (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept. 5; 1p
  - American Library Annual (Box 2)
    see Bowker, R.R.
  - American Mathematical Society, Bulletin (Box 2)
    see Cole, F.N.
  - American Medical Society (Box 2)
    - Protest, 1933 Dec.???; 1p
  - American Mercury (Box 2)
    - Statement of payment for Review: Dangers of Sterilization, 1934 Sept. 21; 1p
      see Hazlitt, Henry
      see Angoff, Charles
  - American Meteorological Soc., Pacific (Box 2)
    - see Young, F.D., 1931 June 19
  - American Museum of Natural History (Box 2)
    - From Wallace, W. Clark, 1888 Dec. 15; 1p
    - Composite letter, 1902
    - ?, 1904 Jan.
    - Re Jessup North Pacific Expedition, 1906 May 24; 5p
    - East Asiatic Comm., 1906 Dec.???
    - Statement of bills, 1909 June 15
    - Corrected of bills, 1909 June 16
    - ?, 1910 Apr. 23
    - Statement, 1913 Mar. 29
    - Account, 1913 Aug. 1
    - Receipt, 1913 Nov. 7
    - Letter?, 1914 Jan. 22
    - Letter?, 1914 June 27; 2p
    - Draft of agreement with Brill, E.J. Co. enc. originally with Lucas, F.A., 1920 Oct. 4
    - Letter?, 1922 Nov. 1; 1p
  - American Philosophical Society (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Apr. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 May 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 May 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Nov. 23; 2p
    - To Boas
    - Notification of membership, 1935 Apr. 19; 1p
    - Agreement for grant, 1941 Dec. 22; 1p
    - Form for Grant to FB, 1942 Nov. 30; 1p
      see Goodspeed, Arthur W.
  - American Psychological Ass'n (Box 2)
    - FB elected member, 1896 Jan. 16
  - American Relief Administration (Box 2)
    - Food drafts, 1920 Mar. 23; 3p
      see Schultz, Wolfram
      see Corn Exchange Bank
      see Herbert Hoover
  - American Relief Comm. for German Children to Germanistic Society of America (Box 2)
    - 1920 Feb., 2p
      see Hepburn, A. Burton
      see Metz, Herman A.
      see Speyer, James
      see Schurz, Carl L.
  - American Rescue Ship Mission (Box 2)
    - see Bryan, Helen R., 1941 Jan. 17
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 19
  - American School in France of Prehistoric Studies (Box 2)
    - see Peabody, C., 1922 Oct.
    - see MacCurdy, G.G., 1930 Jan. 9
  - American Soc. for Cultural Relations with Russia (Box 2)
    see Dell, Floyd
  - American Students Union, New York (Box 2)
    - see Kamaiko, Jack, 1939 July 10
  - American Teacher (Box 2)
    - re Kraus, A.J.I., 1935 Feb.???
  - Ameringer, Oscar (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 18; 1p
  - Ames, E.R. (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1925 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 June 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 July 15; 1p
  - Ames, H.V. (Box 2)
    - 1913 Oct. 20
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 21
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 11
  - Ames, Winthrop (Box 2)
    - From Boas
    - (also sent to Warburg, Paul M. Adams, Edward Kahn, Otto), 1910 Apr. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1910 May 9
  - Ami, H.M. (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1903 June 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 July 21
  - Amira, K. von (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 2
  - Anders, P. (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 4
  - Anderson, Edwin H. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Mar. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 June 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Apr. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 June 9; 1p
  - Anderson, Gunnar (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1904 Mar. 4; 1p
  - Anderson, Harvey W. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1940 May 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 June 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 May 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 8; 1p
  - Anderson, J.E. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 6; 1p
  - Anderson, J.R. & Co. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 31; 1p
  - Anderson, W.P. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Andrade, M.J. (Box 2)
    - 1928 July 25, 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Sep. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Sep 26 & Sept 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 1p
    - From Boas, 1934 Dec. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1935 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 June 27
    - To Boas, 1928 July 14; 3p
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Sept 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 Jan. 23; 5p
    - To Boas, 1935 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 12; 1p
    - To Swadesh, M., 1937 July 11; 3p
  - Andrade, Manuel Velasquez (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1912 June 4
    - To Boas, 1918 May 30; 2p
  - Andree, Richard (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 20; 2p
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 27
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1910 May 4
    - To Boas, 1890 July 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 1; 3p
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 21
    - To Boas, 1910 May 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 14
  - Andrew Freedman Home (Box 2)
    - Rules, enc. with Speyer, Jas., 1925 Dec. 3
  - Andrews, A.B. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 21; 1p
  - Andrews, A.C. (Box 2)
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 19
  - Andrews, Miss H. A. (Box 2)
    (Sec'y, Dept. of Anthropology American Museum of Natural History)
    - From Boas, 1902 Aug. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1905 June 17
    - From Boas, 1905 June 18
    - From Boas, 1905 June 19
    - From Boas, 1905 June 20
    - From Boas, 1905 June 21
    - From Boas, 1905 June 22
    - From Boas, 1905 June 25
    - From Boas, 1905 June 26
    - From Boas, 1905 June 29
    - From Boas, 1905 July 3
    - From Boas, 1905 July 10
    - From Boas, 1906 June 20
    - From Boas, 1910 Dec. 4
    - From Boas, 1913 July 8
    - From Boas, 1913 July 23
    - From Boas, 1913 Sept 10
    - From Boas, 1915 July 6
    - From Boas, 1915 July 7
    - From Boas, 1915 July 7
    - From Boas, 1915 July 8
    - From Boas, 1915 July 13
    - From Boas, 1915 July 13
    - From Boas, 1915 July 14
    - From Boas, 1915 July 14
    - From Boas, 1915 July 17
    - From Boas, 1915 July 20
    - From Boas, 1915 July 22
    - From Boas, 1915 July 29
    - From Boas, 1915 July 31
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 4
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 4
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 18
    - From Boas, 1915 Sep 6 & Aug. 21
    - From Boas, 1915 Aug. 22
    - From Boas, 1916 July 14
    - From Boas, 1916 July 19
    - From Boas, 1916 July 27
    - From Boas, 1916 July 30
    - From Boas, 1916 Aug. 4
    - From Boas, 1916 Aug. 9
    - From Boas, 1916 Aug. 10
    - From Boas, 1916 Aug. 15
    - From Boas, 1916 Aug. 20
    - From Boas, 1916 Aug. 25
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept 1
    - From Boas, 1916 Sept 11
    - From Boas, 1917 June 22
    - From Boas, 1917 June 28
      - Found end of Dec., 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Sept 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1919 Sept 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sept 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Nov. 15 & Nov. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 May 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Apr. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 May 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 June 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1898 July 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1902 Sept 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Sept 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1902 Sept 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1903 June 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 June 19
    - To Boas, 1905 June 21
    - To Boas, 1905 June 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 June 29; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 July 1
    - To Boas, 1905 July 5
    - To Boas, 1905 July 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 3
    - To Boas, 1906 June 27
    - To Boas, 1906 June 28
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 19
    - To Boas, 1909 July 18
    - To Boas, 1909 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1914 July 28
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 8
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 4
    - To Boas, 1914 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1915 July 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 July 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 July 12
    - To Boas, 1915 July 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 July 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 July 15
    - To Boas, 1915 July 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1915 July 19
    - To Boas, 1915 July 20
    - To Boas, 1915 July 21
    - To Boas, 1915 July 22
    - To Boas, 1915 July 23
    - To Boas, 1915 July 26
    - To Boas, 1915 July 29
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 2
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 9
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 11
    - To Boas, 1915 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept 1
    - To Boas, 1915 Sept 8
    - To Boas, 1916 June 20
    - To Boas, 1916 June 26
    - To Boas, 1916 July 15
    - To Boas, 1916 July 10
    - To Boas, 1916 July 20
    - To Boas, 1916 July 21
    - To Boas, 1916 July 26; 2p
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 3
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 7
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 15
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 16
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 23
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept 4
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept 8
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept 13
    - To Boas, 1917 June 20
    - To Boas, 1917 June 22
    - To Boas, 1917 June 25
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 1
    - To Boas, 1917 Sept. 3
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 1
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 8; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Sept. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 1; 4p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 31; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 4; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 21; 1p
      - Found end of Oct., 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 May 7; 4p
    - To Boas, 1921 June 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 July 18; 3p
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 17; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 9; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 29; 5p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 3; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 5; 6p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 16; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Apr. 24; 3p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 May 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 July 26; 4p
    - Barbeau, C.M. -- to Miss Andrews, 1920 Oct. 11; 1p
    - Comer, G. -- from H.A.A., 1906 June 23
    - Frachtenberg, L.G. -- to H.A.A., 1912 Feb. 8
    - Frachtenberg, L.G. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Aug. 17
    - Frachtenberg, L.G. -- to H.A.A., 1912 Feb. 12
    - Frachtenberg, L.G. -- to H.A.A., 1913 June 4
    - Grendon, F. -- to H.A.A., 1909 June 29
    - Hershey, A.H. -- to H.A.A., 1913 May 24
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1900 May 12
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1900 July 30; 1p
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1900 Aug. 7; 1p
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1900 Aug. 8
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1902 Sept 11; 1p
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1902 Sept 27; 1p
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1905 Aug. 16
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1906 Jan. 20
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1915 Feb. 3
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1915 May 29
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1915 June 10
    - Hodge, F.W. -- from H.A.A., 1915 Sept 11
    - Hovey, E.O. -- to H.A.A., 1909 Dec. 16
    - Hunt, Geo. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 31
    - Hunt, Geo. -- from H.A.A., 1901 Aug. 29
    - Hunt, Geo. -- from H.A.A., 1901 Sept 21
    - Hunt, Geo. -- from H.A.A., 1911 Feb. 11
    - Husband, W.W. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 13
    - Husband, W.W. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 14
    - Husband, W.W. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 19
    - Husband, W.W. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 23
    - Husband, W.W. -- from H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 10; 2p
    - Husband, W.W. -- from H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 14; 1p
    - Husband, W.W. -- from H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 16; 1p
    - Husband, W.W. -- from H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 21; 2p
    - Kelsey, F.W., 1911 Feb. 2
    - McGee, W.J. -- from H.A.A., 1901 June 5; 1p
      Dec. 1971 Not in file
    - McGee, W.J. -- from H.A.A., 1902 Aug. 4; 1p
    - Michelson, T. -- to H.A.A., 1912 July 21
    - Michelson, T. -- to H.A.A., 1917 July 16
    - Nassau, R.H. -- to H.A.A., 1917 June 6
    - New Era Printing Co. -- from H.A.A., 1913 May 28
    - New Era Printing Co. -- from H.A.A., 1920 Sept. 17; 1p
    - Penard, T.E. -- to H.A.A., 1917 June 23
    - Pierce, -- from H.A.A., 1901 Sept 3; 1p
    - Putnam's Sons -- from H.A.A., 1902 Sept 19; 1p
    - Radin, P. -- to H.A.A., 1913 Oct. 25
    - Radin, P. -- to H.A.A., 1914 July 15
    - Robbins, Miss -- from H.A.A., 1923 July 24; 2p
    - Seler, E. -- from H.A.A., 1903 June 30; 1p
    - Speck, F.G. -- to H.A., 1912 June 26
    - Stechert, G.E. & Co. -- to H.A.A., 1920 June 3; 1p
    - Swanton, J.R. -- to H.A.A., 1903 June 11
    - Swanton, J.R. -- from H.A.A., 1907 Oct. 7
    - Teit, J.A. -- to H.A.A., 1907 June 22
    - Teit, J.A. -- to H.A.A., 1910 Dec. 13
    - Teit, J.A. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Jan. 16
    - Teit, J.A. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Feb. 16
    - Voth, H.R. -- to H.A.A., 1912 May 23
    - Voth, H.R. -- to H.A.A., 1911 Dec. 15
    - Wallace, Amy -- to H.A.A., 1907 Apr. 8
  - Andrews, J.V. (Mrs. A.B.) (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1933 Sept 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Sept 11; 1p
  - Andrew, John & Son (Box 2)
    - To Hodge, 1909 Apr. 1
  - v. Andrian-Werburg, Freiherr (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1898 Aug. 8; 3p
  - Andron, D.S. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 26; 1p
  - Andrus, Caroline W. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1907 Nov. 27
    - From Boas, 1908 Apr. 23
    - From Boas, 1909 Apr. 2
    - From Boas, 1910 May 2
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 29
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1907 Dec. 1
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 16
    - To Boas, 1909 Apr. 27 (or 24)
    - To Boas, 1909 June 6
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 6
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 5; 2p
  - Anfield, F.E. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 30; 1p
  - Angell, James R. (Box 2)
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 12; 2p
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 27; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Mar. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 19; 1p
    - Bingham, M. -- to J.R.A., 1925 Feb. 18
    - Seligman, E.R. -- from J.R.A., 1926 Mar. 2; 1p